http://www.summacreative.com/privacy

Our WorkAbout UsContact UsPrivacy?Yes, Please.Privacy
Summa Creative, LLC operates the website located at www.summacreative.com (the “site”). This privacy policy describes the information that we collect through our website and how we use that information. By using this website, you indicate your acceptance of the Summa Creative Privacy Policy.Privacy Policy ChangesFrom time to time Summa Creative may need to make changes to our privacy policy, and we reserve the right to make changes without notification.Information We CollectSumma Creative will only collect personally identifiable information (e.g. name, phone number, email) if you expressly submit information to us on our website or through email. Personal data does not include aggregated data or data that, by itself, does not permit the identification of an individual person.What We Do With The Information We Collect Summa Creative will use the personally identifiable information entered on our site for the sole purpose of contacting the person with the design challenge and helping their business.Summa Creative will use aggregated data collected exclusively for marketing analysis of the site, including analytics concerning how users find and use the site.What We Won’t Do With The Information We CollectSumma Creative will never sell or share any collected information with third parties, or bother you with annoying newsletter emails. We all hate that, and we aren’t that kind of people.Links to Other Websites  (Their Crazy Is Not Our Crazy)The Summa Creative site may contain links to other sites. We are not and cannot make any claim or representation regarding, and we accept no responsibility for, the quality, content, nature, or reliability of websites accessible from this site, or websites linking to this site.  Summa Creative does not have control over the information-gathering practices of those sites and visitors should consult privacy policies for those sites.
